# Stephanie Wu

Multidisciplinary illustrator and designer from Boston, MA. Currently a junior at RISD studying everything from watercolor to brand design. My work is informed by personal experiences, fiction, and observation. Outside of studio, you can find me trying Chinese recipes and biking all over Providence.

hello@stephanieswu.com 617-595-0818 stephanieswu.com

## education

Rhode Island School of Design BFA, Illustration 2021 / Providence, RI

## experience

### Artists For Humanity / Exhibitions Assistant

Supported exhibitions and the sales of AFH's art, curated art for clients and AFH's galleries, traveled offsite to install art for clients, devised new painting organization systems, catalouged sales into Salesforce JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019 / BOSTON, MA

#### Brown Political Review / Art Director

Worked in a team of art directors lead by a creative director for student-run political magazine, critiqued sketches and corresponded with illustrators <a href="http://brownpoliticalreview.org/">http://brownpoliticalreview.org/</a>

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT / PROVIDENCE, RI

#### RISD IDSA / Junior Designer

Collaborated with the lead designer for the RISD chapter of Industrial Designers Society of America, created marketing materials, worked on club rebranding and identity

FEBRUARY 2019- PRESENT / PROVIDENCE, RI

#### Brown Daily Herald Post / Staff Illustrator

Published weekly editorial and cover illustrations for the student run arts magazine at Brown University post.browndailyherald.com/

## software

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign After Effects Lightroom Premiere Pro HTML CSS Javascript Processing Google Suite

## capabilities

art direction
editorial illustration
risograph printing
web design
brand identity
motion graphics
surface design
letterpress printing
kinetic typography
art installation
Mandarin Chinese